Guide to the Archives of the Soviet communist party and Soviet state microfilm collection: Russian State Archives of Social and Political History (Rossiiskii gosudarstvennyi arkhiv sotsialno-politicheskoi istorii - RGASPI)
Hoover Institution Archives
- Fond 17, The Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union records, 1903-1965; 1971; 2,457 reels
  - Opis 9: Department of Registration and Statistics., 1422 reels) (Reel 2.188-2.317, Reel 2.645-2.733, Reel 2.802-2.870, Reel 2.999-2.1095, Reel 2.1421-2.1486, Reel 2.1551-2.2434, Reel 2.639-2.2770)
    - Georgian Soviet Socailist Republic
      - Amirkhanov Ovanes - Afanasiev Semen (Reel 2.732, File 615-618)
      - Aflatun-ogly-Binali - Barbakadze (Reel 2.733, File 618-621)
      - Barbakhadze - Berikashvili (Reel 2.802, File 621-624)
      - Berinov - Buachidze, A.S (Reel 2.803, File 624-627)
      - Buachidze A. M - Vegiapidze (Reel 2.804, File 627-630)
      - Vegiapidze, Shota - Ganevich (Reel 2.805, File 630-633)
      - Ganeev - Georgadze, I. G. (Reel 2.806, File 633-636)
      - Georgadze, I. D. - Gogoladze, S. A. (Reel 2.807, File 636-639)
      - Gogoladze, M. G - Gudadze, G. P. (Reel 2.808, File 639-642)
      - Gudadze, V. S. - Darchiia, A. L. (Reel 2.809, File 642-645)
      - Darchiia, I.S. - Dzhaparidze, S. G. (Reel 2.810, File 645-648)
      - Dzhaparidze, A. G. - Dzindzibadze (Reel 2.811, File 648-651)
      - Dzieladze - Dzineladze (Reel 2.812, File 652-654)
      - Yelgozov - Iadirashvili (Reel 2.813, File 654-657)
      - Iadze - Kakauridze, B. Ie (Reel 2.814, File 657-660)
      - Kakauridze, B. G. - Kartvelishvili, S. G. (Reel 2.815, File 660-662)
      - Kartvelishvili, L.A. - Kekelidze, S.M. (Reel 2.816, File 662-665)
      - Kekelidze, N. L. - Kldiashvili, S.G. (Reel 2.817, File 665-668)
      - Kldiashvili, G. N. - Kostandov (Reel 2.818, File 668-671)
      - Kostenko - Kurulov (Reel 2.819, File 671-673)
      - Kurkhuli - Lozovoi (Reel 2.820, File 674-677)
      - Lozunov - Malechkina (Reel 2.821, File 677-680)
      - Maliants - Maul (Reel 2.822, File 680-682)
      - Makhagadze - Merkviladze (Reel 2.823, File 683-686)
      - Merkulov - Modebadze, D. I. (Reel 2.824, File 686-689)
      - Modebadze, V. I. - Nadiradze, P. G. (Reel 2.825, File 689-692)
      - Nadiradze, I.,S - Nucheshidze (Reel 2.826, File 692-694)
      - Obgadze - Papuashvili G. S. (Reel 2.827, File 695-698)
      - Papuashvili, G.Ia. - Poplavskii (Reel 2.828, File 698-700)
      - Popov - Rurua, P.G. (Reel 2.829, File 701-703)
      - Rurua, N. P. - Sarduashvili (Reel 2.830, File 703-706)
      - Sarukhanov - Snitko (Reel 2.831, File 706-708)
      - Sobaev - Takaev, S. A. (Reel 2.832, File 709-711)
      - Takaev, S. G. - Tkapladze (Reel 2.833, File 711-714)
      - Tkachenko - Urtkmelidze (Reel 2.834, File 714-717)
      - Urtmelidze - Khvadagiani, Sh. A. (Reel 2.835, File 717-721)
      - Khvadagiani V.S. - Khushpulian (Reel 2.836, File 721-724)
      - Tsaava - Tsurukian (Reel 2.837, File 725-727)
      - Tsurtsumpa - Chelidze, D. S. (Reel 2.838, File 728-731)
      - Chelidze, S. Ia. - Churadze, S. M (Reel 2.839, File 731-733)
      - Churadze, O. I. - Shakharashvili (Reel 2.840, File 733-736)
      - Shkhbazov - Yakovlev A. (Reel 2.841, File 736-739)
      - Yakovlev, B. - Yashvili (Reel 2.842, File 739)
    - Dagestan Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in the Dagestan Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republi
      - Aishakhanov - Alieva (Reel 2.842, File 740-741)
      - Alikebedov - Gasanov Mekhti (Reel 2.843, File 742-745)
      - Gasanov Mirza - Isaev, Dav. (Reel 2.844, File 745-748)
      - Isaev, Dzh. - Magomaev Abdulla (Reel 2.845, File 748-751)
      - Magomaev Absalutdin - Nazaraliev Abdulselim (Reel 2.846, File 751-754)
      - Nazaraliev Akhmed - Sirotkin (Reel 2.847, File 754-757)
      - Skazinov - Shamkhalov (Reel 2.848, File 758-760)
      - Shanavazov - Yashchenko (Reel 2.849, File 761)
    - Dalnevostochnyi krai
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Dalnevostochnyi krai (Far-East Territory)
      - Abakov - Anoprienko (Reel 2.849, File 762-763)
      - Anosov - Bashurov (Reel 2.850, File 764-766)
      - Bebenin - Borodin, A. Ia. (Reel 2.851, File 767-770)
      - Borodin, A.S. - Vasilieva (Reel 2.852, File 770-773)
      - Vasilevskii - Viatkin (Reel 2.853, File 774-776)
      - Gabinskaia - Gorkovenko, Karp (Reel 2.854, File 777-780)
      - Gorkovenko Filip - Demidov (Reel 2.855, File 780-783)
      - Demura - Yelisefenko (Reel 2.856, File 784-787)
      - Yeliseev - Zaiats (Reel 2.857, File 787-789)
      - Zban - Ionov A. T. (Reel 2.858, File 790-793)
      - Ionov, G. M. - Kechinov (Reel 2.859, File 793-796)
      - Kibirev - Kovalenko (Reel 2.860, File 797-799)
      - Kovbaska - Korelin (Reel 2.861, File 800-802)
      - Korenev - Ksenzik (Reel 2.862, File 802-804)
      - Kubarkov - Laperdin, V. A. (Reel 2.863, File 805-807)
      - Laperdin, I. A. - Lomonosov (Reel 2.864, File 807-811)
      - Lomov - Marokulin (Reel 2.865, File 811-814)
      - Marskii - Mikhailov (Reel 2.866, File 815-818)
      - Mikhalenko - Nemilostivyi G.I (Reel 2.867, File 818-822)
      - Nemilostivyi G. I. - Omelianenko (Reel 2.868, File 822-825)
      - Onasenko - Perederii (Reel 2.869, File 826-829)
      - Perevodhikov - Polozov (Reel 2.870, File 829-832)
      - Polkratov - Piatyshina (Reel 2.999, File 832-835)
      - Rabenau - Savitskii A. F. (Reel 2.1000, File 836-838)
      - Savitskii A. P. - Seialov (Reel 2.1001, File 838-841)
      - Si - Soialin (Reel 2.1002, File 842-844)
      - Spirin - Tezikov (Reel 2.1003, File 845-847)
      - Tetugin - Tia (Reel 2.1004, File 847-849)
      - Ukhalov - Khudiakov (Reel 2.1005, File 850-852)
      - Khlestkina - Chetverikov (Reel 2.1006, File 852-854)
      - Chernogorenko - Shevtsov (Reel 2.1007, File 855-856)
      - Shekoldin - Yampolskii (Reel 2.1008, File 857-859)
      - Yakobson - Yakovlev (Reel 2.1009, File 859)
    - Ivanovo-Voznesenskaia guberniia
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Ivanovo-Voznesenskaia guberniia
      - Abaimov - Ashurin (Reel 2.1009, File 860-861)
      - Babin - Beliaev (Reel 2.1010, File 862-864)
      - Benkler - Biakov (Reel 2.1011, File 864-867)
      - Vanin - Voronezhev (Reel 2.1012, File 868-870)
      - Voronkin - Gochin (Reel 2.1013, File 870-873)
      - Grechin - Dmitriev (Reel 2.1014, File 874-876)
      - Dozhdikov - Zhmurchenko (Reel 2.1015, File 877-879)
      - Zhitikova - Ivanova (Reel 2.1016, File 979-882)
      - Ivancheva - Kashin (Reel 2.1017, File 882-884)
      - Kvasnikov - Komissarov (Reel 2.1018, File 885-887)
      - Komissarova - Koshkin (Reel 2.1019, File 887-889)
      - Krasnov - Kulikov N. A. (Reel 2.1020, File 890-892)
      - Kulikov A. V. - Liberan (Reel 2.1021, File 892-894)
      - Lisina - Marinin (Reel 2.1022, File 894-897)
      - Mariin - Molkov (Reel 2.1023, File 897-899)
      - Morozov - Novozhilov (Reel 2.1024, File 899-902)
      - Novikov - Pevtsov (Reel 2.1025, File 902-905)
      - Petrov - Puzanov (Reel 2.1026, File 905-907)
      - Pudikov - Riabinin (Reel 2.1027, File 907-909)
      - Sabaev - Sizova, Matrena (Reel 2.1028, File 910-912)
      - Sizova, Anna - Soloviev (Reel 2.1029, File 912-914)
      - Sobolev - Synkov (Reel 2.1030, File 915-916)
      - Tarasov - Urusov (Reel 2.1031, File 917-920)
      - Uranova - Tsyganenko (Reel 2.1032, File 920-923)
      - Tsykina - Shvetsov (Reel 2.1033, File 923-925)
      - Shestunin - Yakovlev (Reel 2.1034, File 926-928)
    - Kazakh Soviet Socialist Republic
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in the Kazakh Soviet Socialist Republic
      - Aazhibaev - Aitasov (Reel 2.1035, File 929-931)
      - Aimanov - Aldzhanov (Reel 2.1036, File 931-933)
      - Ameltchenko - Atildzhanov (Reel 2.1037, File 934-936)
      - Atakhodzhiev - Beidanov (Reel 2.1038, File 936-939)
      - Baidakov - Bashtakov (Reel 2.1039, File 939-941)
      - Bashakbaeva - Berezin (Reel 2.1040, File 941-943)
      - Berimbetov - Bobrovnikov (Reel 2.1041, File 944-946)
      - Borisov - Vdovin (Reel 2.1042, File 946-948)
      - Verkhodub - Galiev (Reel 2.1043, File 949-951)
      - Garbunov - Grabovskii (Reel 2.1044, File 951-953)
      - Grigorieva - Derebiaga (Reel 2.1045, File 954-956)
      - Demurenko - Dzhuliubaev (Reel 2.1046, File 956-959)
      - Dzhumabekov - Dubinin (Reel 2.1047, File 959-962)
      - Duisebaev - Yeshchenko (Reel 2.1048, File 962-964)
      - Zharylgapov - Zarinbo (Reel 2.1049, File 965-967)
      - Zaika - Ivanov (Reel 2.1050, File 967-969)
      - Iglikov - Islamboniev (Reel 2.1051, File 970-972)
      - Ismanilova - Kalinkina (Reel 2.1052, File 973-975)
      - Kamletdenova - Kariakina (Reel 2.1053, File 976-977)
      - Kaskenov - Knaub (Reel 2.1054, File 978-980)
      - Kobirov - Konkin (Reel 2.1055, File 981-983)
      - Kononenko - Krainova (Reel 2.1056, File 983-986)
      - Kravchenko - Kultemidov (Reel 2.1057, File 986-988)
      - Kulbatynov - Larshin (Reel 2.1058, File 988-991)
      - Laumullin - Liamin (Reel 2.1059, File 991-993)
      - Mavlianberdyev - Masalimov (Reel 2.1060, File 994-996)
      - Masatov - Mirgusmanov (Reel 2.1061, File 996-998)
      - Mikhalskii - Mukhamedzhanov (Reel 2.1062, File 998-1000)
      - Mustafin - Nerush (Reel 2.1063, File 1001-1003)
      - Nesterov - Niazbekov (Reel 2.1064, File 1003-1005)
      - Obitov - Parbuzin (Reel 2.1065, File 1006-1008)
      - Peregudov - Poliakov (Reel 2.1066, File 1009-1011)
      - Pokhomov - Raimkulov (Reel 2.1067, File 1011-1014)
      - Rakhmetov - Riabinin (Reel 2.1068, File 1014-1016)
      - Sabetov - Sarbasov (Reel 2.1069, File 1017-1019)
      - Sartaev - Sergeev (Reel 2.1070, File 1019-1022)
      - Sentin - Snopov (Reel 2.1071, File 1022-1024)
      - Sokolov - Sultanbaev (Reel 2.1072, File 1024-1027)
      - Sultantemirov - Telegina (Reel 2.1073, File 1027-1030)
      - Teliapova - Proshin (Reel 2.1074, File 1030-1032)
      - Travkin - Uksukbaev (Reel 2.1075, File 1032-1035)
      - Ukushev - Ushokpaev (Reel 2.1076, File 1035-1037)
      - Fakhrutdinov - Khvostov (Reel 2.1077, File 1038-1040)
      - Khizhniak - Chemesova (Reel 2.1078, File 1041-1043)
      - Chelymbekova - Sharipov (Reel 2.1079, File 1043-1046)
      - Shaukin - Shyntaeva (Reel 2.1080, File 1046-1048)
      - Shcherbakov - Yamin (Reel 2.1081, File 1049-1050)
    - Kalmyk Autonomous oblast
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Kalmyk Autonomous oblast
      - Abramov- Borochkaev (Reel 2.1081, File 1051)
      - Bosongov - Badmaev (Reel 2.1082, File 1051-1054)
      - Sarangov - Yashkulov (Reel 2.1083, File 1054-1055)
    - Kaluzhskaia guberniia
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Kaluzhskaia guberniia
      - Abarshalin - Barantsev Anatolii (Reel 2.1083, File 1056-1057)
      - Barantsev Ivan - Gerasimova (Reel 2.1084, File 1057-1060)
      - Gerasimovich - Zhokhov (Reel 2.1085, File 1060-1063)
      - Zhuravlev - Kozlov Nikolai (Reel 2.1086, File 1063-1966)
      - Kozlov Ivan - Leonov Tikhon (Reel 2.1087, File 1066-1069)
      - Leonov - Nikolatin (Reel 2.1088, File 1069-1072)
      - Nikolashin - Rozhkov (Reel 2.1089, File 1072-1075)
      - Rozhkov Nikolai - Stepanova (Reel 2.1090, File 1075-1077)
      - Stepaniuk - Titov (Reel 2.1091, File 1078-1080)
      - Chavchavadze - Yatsinin (Reel 2.1092, File 1081-1082)
    - Karelskaia Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in the Karelskaia Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      - Asanova - Barmin (Reel 2.1092, File 1083-1084)
      - Bukhalov - Ivacheva (Reel 2.1093, File 1084-1086)
      - Karabanin - Mikhailov (Reel 2.1094, File 1087-1090)
      - Muntuev - Sviridov (Reel 2.1095, File 1090-1093)
      - Savinov - Yakushov (Reel 2.1421, File 1093-1095)
    - Kirgiz Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in the Kirgiz Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      - Abaev - Bokuev Dovletabai (Reel 2.1422, File 1096-1098)
      - Bokuev Sultambek - Dzhangarachev (Reel 2.1423, File 1098-1000)
      - Yegemberdeev - Kozlov (Reel 2.1424, File 1101-1103)
      - Kvochkin - Naimanov (Reel 2.1425, File 1103-1106)
      - Nasibulin - Sandybaev (Reel 2.1426, File 1106-1109)
      - Suranchiev - Khusainov (Reel 2.1427, File 1109-1112)
      - Khodzhabekov - Yakimenko (Reel 2.1428, File 1112-1113)
    - Komi-Zyrianskaia Autonomous Oblast
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in the Komi-Zyrianskaia Autonomous Oblast
      - Agafonova - Zubov (Reel 2.1428, File 1114)
      - Ivanov - Rocheva (Reel 2.1429, File 1115-1117)
      - Saveliev - Yachmenev (Reel 2.1430, File 1118-1119)
    - Kostromskaia guberniia
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Kostromskaia guberniia
      - Abaimov - Beliaev (Reel 2.1430, File 1120-1121)
      - Bunteev - Gruzdev (Reel 2.1431, File 1121-1123)
      - Dobronravin - Komilov (Reel 2.1432, File 1124-1126)
      - Kordakov - Leontiev (Reel 2.1433, File 1127-1129)
      - Latyshev - Polozov (Reel 2.1434, File 1129-1132)
      - Poletaev - Smirnov (Reel 2.1435, File 1132-1134)
      - Smirnova - Tsvetkova, Natalia (Reel 2.1436, File 1135-1137)
      - Tsvetkova, Anna - Yakhonin (Reel 2.1437, File 1137-1138)
    - Crimean Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in the Crimean Autonomous Soviet Socialist Republic
      - Ablaev - Abindenko (Reel 2.1437, File 1139-1140)
      - Abramovich - Biakin (Reel 2.1438, File 1140-1142)
      - Vnukov - Gritsko (Reel 2.1439, File 1143-1145)
      - Gritsenko - Zaitseva (Reel 2.1440, File 1145-1148)
      - Zekki - Klochkova (Reel 2.1441, File 1148-1151)
      - Klimov - Kianskii (Reel 2.1442, File 1151-1153)
      - Lisovskii - Mezis (Reel 2.1443, File 1154-1155)
      - Meksin - Orazov (Reel 2.1444, File 1156-1157)
      - Parshukovskii - Paltsevich (Reel 2.1445, File 1158-1160)
      - Radionov - Steblianko (Reel 2.1446, File 1160-1163)
      - Stasiuk - Filatov (Reel 2.1447, File 1163-1165)
      - Khasai - Shulkin (Reel 2.1448, File 1166-1167)
      - Sherstiakov - Yakub (Reel 2.1449, File 1167-1168)
    - Kurskaia guberniia
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Kurskaia guberniia
      - Abolmasov - Baryshev (Reel 2.1449, File 1169-1170)
      - Banchukov - Butusov (Reel 2.1450, File 1170-1173)
      - Bukin - Golozubova (Reel 2.1451, File 1173-1176)
      - Golovacheva - Yeremenko (Reel 2.1452, File 1176-1179)
      - Yeskov - Ivanilov (Reel 2.1453, File 1179-1181)
      - Katalnikov - Kozlov (Reel 2.1454, File 1182-1184)
      - Koroblev - Lomonosov (Reel 2.1455, File 1184-1186)
      - Luzanov - Masalov (Reel 2.1456, File 1187-1189)
      - Mezentsev - Penkov (Reel 2.1457, File 1189-1192)
      - Perekrestov - Rutskoi (Reel 2.1458, File 1192-1194)
      - Riabtsev - Sorokoletov (Reel 2.1459, File 1194-1197)
      - Sologub - Frolov (Reel 2.1460, File 1197-1200)
      - Fateev - Shevliakov (Reel 2.1461, File 1200-1203)
      - Shukshin - Yakovlev (Reel 2.1462, File 1203-1204)
    - Lenigradskai gubernia and the City of Leningrad
      Questionnaries filled out by VKP(b) members and candidate members during the 1926-1927 party census in Lenigradskai guberniia and the city of Leningrad
      - Aalto - Avlasovich (Reel 2.1462, File 1205-1206)
      - Avrunina - Akentieva (Reel 2.1463, File 1206-1208)
      - Alabushev - Alekseev (Reel 2.1464, File 1209-1211)
      - Alekseev-Bushin - Aman (Reel 2.1465, File 1211-1213)
      - Amon - Andreeva, Aleksandra (Reel 2.1466, File 1213-1216)
      - Andreeva, Tatiana - Antonov, Nikolai (Reel 2.1467, File 1216-1218)
      - Antonov, Boris - Arkhipov (Reel 2.1468, File 1219-1221)
      - Arsenieva - Aiukhina-Kanaeva (Reel 2.1469, File 1221-1223)
      - Babkin - Balin (Reel 2.1470, File 1224-1226)
      - Baliasnikov - Baryshnikov (Reel 2.1471, File 1226-1229)
      - Baryshev - Bellert (Reel 2.1472, File 1229-1231)
      - Belova - Benia (Reel 2.1473, File 1232-1233)
      - Bernan - Blankenburg (Reel 2.1474, File 1224-1235)
      - Bobrov - Boldemov (Reel 2.1475, File 1236-1238)
      - Bogdanov - Boltushkin (Reel 2.1476, File 1238-1240)
      - Bolinskii - Borisov (Reel 2.1477, File 1241-1242)
      - Bosov - Bukvarev (Reel 2.1478, File 1243-1245)
      - Bukas - Buianskaia (Reel 2.1479, File 1245-1247)
      - Bydzap - Varga (Reel 2.1480, File 1248-1250)
      - Varfolomeev - Vasiliev, Iosif (Reel 2.1481, File 1250-1252)
      - Vasiliev, Ivan - Vasilchikov (Reel 2.1482, File 1252-1254)
      - Vasilchenko - Vetrov Dmitrii (Reel 2.1483, File 1254-1256)
      - Vetrov, Luka - Vikhrov (Reel 2.1484, File 1256-1259)
      - Vikhko - Volkov, Aleksei (Reel 2.1485, File 1259-1261)
      - Volkov, Ivan - Vorontsov, Matvei (Reel 2.1486, File 1261-1264)
      - Vorontsov, Dmitrii - Gaitsoki (Reel 2.1551, File 1264-1267)
      - Gailish - Georgiev (Reel 2.1552, File 1267-1269)
      - German - Goldakovskii (Reel 2.1553, File 1270-1272)
      - Goldin - Gorbunov (Reel 2.1554, File 1272-1274)
      - Gorbushin - Grachev Ivan (Reel 2.1555, File 1275-1277)
      - Grachev, Mikhail - Grigorshin (Reel 2.1556, File 1277-1279)
      - Gridasov - Gudreish (Reel 2.1557, File 1280-1282)
      - Gudiev - Giach (Reel 2.1558, File 1282-1284)
      - Dabuzhskii - Dementiev Sergei (Reel 2.1559, File 1285-1287)
      - Dementiev Ivan - Dmitriev Ivan (Reel 2.1560, File 1287-1290)
      - Dmitriev Foma - Domiian (Reel 2.1561, File 1290-1292)
      - Don - Dumchin (Reel 2.1562, File 1293-1295)
      - Dunaev - Yegorov Semen (Reel 2.1563, File 1296-1298)
      - Yegorov Fedor - Yelin (Reel 2.1564, File 1298-1300)
      - Yelizarov - Yershov Vladimir (Reel 2.1565, File 1300-1303)
      - Yershov Grigorii - Zhechnevskaia (Reel 2.1566, File 1303-1305)
      - Zheludova - Zhuravlev Georgii (Reel 2.1567, File 1306-1308)
      - Zhuravlev Nikandr - Zaitseva (Reel 2.1568, File 1308-1310)
      - Zakrzhevskii - Zviagin (Reel 2.1569, File 1311-1313)
      - Zverev - Zovvulov (Reel 2.1570, File 1313-1316)
      - Zrublevskii - Ivanov, Vasilii (Reel 2.1571, File 1317-1319)
      - Ivanov, Vladimir - Ivanov, Mikhail Kh. (Reel 2.1572, File 1319-1322)
      - Ivanov Mikhail Iv. - Ivanov, Iakov (Reel 2.1573, File 1322-1324)
      - Ivanova - Ignatiev (Reel 2.1574, File 1325-1327)
      - Igoshin - Ioganson (Reel 2.1575, File 1328-1330)
      - Ionchik - Kazakov (Reel 2.1576, File 1330-1332)
      - Kainov - Kanev (Reel 2.1577, File 1333-1335)
      - Kaniukov - Karstina (Reel 2.1578, File 1335-1337)
      - Kartashov - Keilin (Reel 2.1579, File 1338-1340)
      - Keek - Kiseleva (Reel 2.1598, File 1340-1343)
      - Kislov - Kobzev (Reel 2.1599, File 1343-1346)
      - Kovalev - Kozlova (Reel 2.1600, File 1346-1348)
      - Kozlov - Kolychkov (Reel 2.1601, File 1348-1350)
      - Komarnitskii - Kononov (Reel 2.1602, File 1351-1353)
      - Konovalov - Korneev (Reel 2.1603, File 1352-1355)
      - Korolev - Kosterin (Reel 2.1604, File 1356-1358)
      - Kosmadel - Krasnoshchek (Reel 2.1605, File 1358-1361)
      - Krasavin - Krutilev (Reel 2.1606, File 1361-1364)
      - Kruglov - Kudriavtsev (Reel 2.1607, File 1364-1366)
      - Kudriakov - Kuznetsov Sergei (Reel 2.1608, File 1367-1369)
      - Kuznetsov Ivan - Kulikov (Reel 2.1609, File 1369-1372)
      - Kulakova - Kurkianet (Reel 2.1610, File 1372-1374)
      - Kurochkin - Lazovskaia, Mariia (Reel 2.1611, File 1374-1377)
      - Lazovskaia, Anna - Lashchevskii (Reel 2.1612, File 1377-1379)
      - Leontieva - Lezova (Reel 2.1613, File 1380-1382)
      - Lezin - Lill (Reel 2.1614, File 1382-1385)
      - Lilinder - Lokotskii (Reel 2.1615, File 1385-1388)
      - Loktev - Lupanov (Reel 2.1616, File 1388-1390)
      - Lurie - Makerevich (Reel 2.1617, File 1391-1393)
      - Makarov - Mamotin (Reel 2.1618, File 1393-1396)
      - Malinin - Markova (Reel 2.1619, File 1396-1398)
      - Markovskaia - Matveev Petr (Reel 2.1620, File 1398-1400)
      - Matveev Dmitrii - Mezhazakis (Reel 2.1621, File 1401-1403)
      - Mezhev - Mikulich (Reel 2.1622, File 1403-1406)
      - Mikkolen - Mikhailov Mikhail (Reel 2.1623, File 1406-1409)
      - Mikhailov Petr - Mikhailova Ielizaveta (Reel 2.1624, File 1409-1411)
      - Mikhailova Vasilisa - Molotov (Reel 2.1625, File 1411-1414)
      - Molchanov - Mrachkovskii (Reel 2.1626, File 1416-1417)
      - Muglin - Nagumanov (Reel 2.1627, File 1417-1419)
      - Nadezhin - Nelichko (Reel 2.1628, File 1419-1422)
      - Nechaeva - Nikitin (Reel 2.1629, File 1422-1424)
      - Nikiforov - Nikolaeva, Antonina (Reel 2.1630, File 1425-1427)
      - Nikolaeva, Aleksandra - Novikov (Reel 2.1631, File 1427-1429)
      - Noev - Ozolin (Reel 2.1632, File 1430-1432)
      - Ozolin Ian - Osinin (Reel 2.1633, File 1432-1435)
      - Osinovskii - Pavlov, Georgii (Reel 2.1634, File 1435-1438)
      - Pavlov, Iurii - Pankratov-Bagun (Reel 2.1635, File 1438-1441)
      - Panfilov - Paianen (Reel 2.1636, File 1441-1443)
      - Pebo - Petrov V. P. (Reel 2.1637, File 1444-1447)
      - Petrov V. A. - Petrova (Reel 2.1638, File 1447-1450)
      - Petrova-Kapustina - Picherin (Reel 2.1639, File 1450-1452)
      - Pinaevskii - Pozdniakov, Ivan (Reel 2.1640, File 1453-1455)
      - Pozdniakov, Petr - Popov, Fedor (Reel 2.1641, File 1455-1458)
      - Popov, Vladimir - Prizhimov (Reel 2.1642, File 1458-1461)
      - Priman - Puzyrev-Khaletskii (Reel 2.1643, File 1461-1464)
      - Pulliainen - Razguliaeva (Reel 2.1644, File 1464-1466)
      - Raikova - Rzhanov (Reel 2.1645, File 1467-1469)
      - Rzhavskii - Romzin (Reel 2.1646, File 1469-1472)
      - Romasheva - Rumiantsev, Petr (Reel 2.1647, File 1472-1474)
      - Rumiantsev, Nikolai - Riabchenko (Reel 2.1648, File 1475-1477)
      - Riabkov - Sazykin, Dmitrii (Reel 2.1649, File 1477-1480)
      - Sazykin, Georgii - Safronov (Reel 2.1650, File 1480-1482)
      - Sakharovskii - Semenov, Nikolai (Reel 2.1651, File 1483-1485)
      - Semenov, Stepan - Sergeev, Ilia (Reel 2.1652, File 1485-1488)
      - Sergeev, Filipp - Sidorov, Ivan (Reel 2.1653, File 1488-1490)
      - Sidorov, Semen - Siel (Reel 2.1654, File 1490-1492)
      - Skakunov - Smirnov, Artemii (Reel 2.1655, File 1493-1495)
      - Smirnov, Aleksandr - Smirnova, Anna (Reel 2.1656, File 1495-1497)
      - Smirnova, Anna F. - Sokolov, Aleksandr (Reel 2.1657, File 1498-1500)
      - Sokolov, Petr - Solovieva, Ielizaveta (Reel 2.1658, File 1500-1503)
      - Solovieva, Nadezhda - Srukhov (Reel 2.1659, File 1503-1505)
      - Stabrovskii - Stepanov Ivan (Reel 2.1660, File 1506-1508)
      - Stepanov Georgii - Suvorov Vasilii (Reel 2.1661, File 1508-1511)
      - Suvorov Aleksei - Sysoev (Reel 2.1662, File 1511-1514)
      - Sysoliatin - Terskaia-Vytskaia (Reel 2.1663, File 1514-1517)
      - Terekhova - Timofeeva (Reel 2.1664, File 1517-1520)
      - Timoshina - Tomchik (Reel 2.1665, File 1520-1523)
      - Tortsev - Trotskii (Reel 2.1666, File 1523-1526)
      - Tropin - Tiurin (Reel 2.1667, File 1526-1529)
      - Tiushin - Utkin (Reel 2.1668, File 1529-1532)
      - Utekhin - Fedorov, I. Al. (Reel 2.1669, File 1532-1535)
      - Fedorov, I. An. - Fedorov (Reel 2.1670, File 1535-1538)